NIKITA VOLOSHENKO

MOBILE DEVELOPMENT ENGINEER

CONTACT

STIVENS54@GMAIL.COM

nikitavoloshenko.com







PROFILE

I am an experienced, motivated and highly dedicated Software Engineer undergraduate student with an ongoing mobile development internship and 2 years of experience in customer service and technical & software support.

Have interest in mobile, system, and game development.

EXPERIENCE



MOBILE ENGINEER

SILICON SPECTRA, SUNNYVALE, CA

OCT 2017 - PRESENT

- Designing and building cross platform messenger for business and corporate communication
- iOS, Android, Firebase, Golang
- Team work, Slack, git

LAB ASSISTANT

DE ANZA COLLEGE LIBRARY, CUPERTINO, CA JAN 2014 - JUN 2016

- · Communication with students from various socioeconomic and cultural backgrounds
- Ability to quickly troubleshoot hardware and software related problems
- Collaboration with faculty members and teamwork

EDUCATION



BS. SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

SAN JOSE STATE UNIVERSITY, SAN JOSE, CA

2017 - 2018

AS. COMPUTER INFORMATION SYSTEMS

DE ANZA COLLEGE, CUPERTINO, CA

2014 - 2016



□ SKILLS

- C++, Java, Python, Swift, Node JS Reliable and responsible
- Mac, Windows, Linux
- Android Studio, Visual Studio, Sublime Text, IDEA, git, vim, npm, AWS, Selenium, JUnit
- Quick learner, self-starter, and result oriented
- Web content development
- Strong oral and writing skills

PROJECTS

CRIME REPORT, BERKELEY HACK, BERKELEY, CA

Implemented a system that predicts and warns user about danger level in their area using public APIs. Facebook Bot Platform, NeighborhoodScout API, Python.

KOMYTT, UCLA HACK, LOS ANGELES, CA.

APR 2017

Web/mobile platform for creating and implementing small-scale jobs in real time with geolocation emphasis targeting temporary jobs market (\$130 billion yearly). iOS. PubNub. Heroku.

CROWD DJ, UC SANTA CRUZ HACK, LOS ANGELES, CA. JAN 2017

Maintained and facilitated development of web service for music flow control in large environments with geographic control. HTML, CSS, Spotify API, Heroku.